foreign
down almost 50 odd points so from the
highs of today's trading session it's
down over 125 odd points but from the
lows it is up around 75 points too so
middling ground is what we're seeing out
there let's talk about one of the stocks
which is Bucking the trend the overall
trend which is ICICI Pro live got a
lease of life in the middle of trade as
the new boss has been announced I know
bakchi gets appointed as MD and CEO Yash
is here with his details Yash up five
percent today what is the street like so
much in him well that's correct uh to
start with an interesting fact when NS
Canon the current uh MD and CEO at I
prove life was appointed he was also the
Ed at ICICI Bank and similar is the case
with Aloo bakchi who's currently the
idiot ICICI Bank and has been appointed
as the next mdn CEO at icic Prudential
life insurance before I come to at the
point on what the street likes about the
disappointment let me just speak a
little about Anup bhakti he will take
over as the mdn CEO of Asia Bank from
June 19th June 18th is when NS Canon
will superannuate his term as MD and CEO
of the company speaking about Anup
bakshi himself he has a management
degree from IIM Bangalore engineering
degree from IIT kanpur he joined the
ICICI group in 1992 and currently as I
said he's the executive director at
ICICI Bank and non-executive director at
icsa potential life insurance itself he
heads the wholesale and transaction
banking markets group and proprietary
trading group also he served as MD and
CEO of icici's Securities uh technically
speaking about his work he's worked in
almost every segment of financial
services space retail banking treasury
Investment Banking small scale industry
payments and settlement systems wealth
management business and it is this point
which the street really is touring today
since a person who will be heading Isis
a potential life has knowledge
understanding and practical experience
from almost every part of the Financial
Services space this is what the street
likes the stock hasn't done well under
uh under NS Canon and that is something
which the street is looking at a change
on that particular aspect as well as
business aspects there is expected to be
more focused on the top line growth
which is the premium growth apart from
the different fundamentals coming down
the road
is a veteran right in the banking
industry so I guess uh two thumbs up to
icic approved post uh the naming
anubhakshi as mbn CEO and that's also
for a period of five years thanks a lot
Yash for that let's do a quick break on
the other side Manisha Gupta will join
in she has with us sushant Gupta
director at wood McKenzie do stay tuned
for that
foreign
[Music]